question_data = [{"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Greenland is almost as big as Africa.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Faust is a playable character in &quot;Guilty Gear Xrd Revelator&quot;.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Brezhnev was the 5th leader of the USSR.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Studio Ghibli is a Japanese animation studio responsible for the films &quot;Wolf Children&quot; and &quot;The Boy and the Beast&quot;.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "The United States Department of Homeland Security was formed in response to the September 11th attacks.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "In &quot;Sonic Adventure&quot;, you are able to transform into Super Sonic at will after completing the main story.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "The Xenomorph from the science fiction film &quot;Alien&quot; has acidic blood.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "In 2010, Twitter and the United States Library of Congress partnered together to archive every tweet by American citizens.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "When you cry in space, your tears stick to your face.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "The end credits sequence in Grand Theft Auto 5 is over half an hour long.", "correct_answer": "True",
                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                           "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "EDM label Monstercat signs tracks instead of artists.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Vehicles", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Ferrari has never made a V10 engine for any of its cars.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "In the video game &quot;Transistor&quot;, &quot;Red&quot; is the name of the main character.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Art", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Leonardo da Vinci was not the creator of the Mona Lisa.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Vehicles", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "BMW M GmbH is a subsidiary of BMW AG that focuses on car performance.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Night on Bald Mountain was one of the musical pieces featured in Disney&#039;s 1940&#039;s film Fantasia.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Popcorn was invented in 1871 by Frederick W. Rueckheim in the USA where he sold the snack on the streets of Chicago.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "The video game &quot;Fuel&quot; has an open world that is 5,560 square miles?", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "&quot;Buffalo buffalo Buffalo buffalo buffalo buffalo Buffalo buffalo.&quot; is a grammatically correct sentence.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Animals", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "The internet browser Firefox is named after the Red Panda.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
